Guide to the Yoshio Kishi Papers MSS.351
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Personal Materials, 1922-2009
  - Kishi, Isomi, 1988, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Kishi, Mitsuo, 1995, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Kudaka, Geraldine N., 1981-1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Kuo, Nina - Postcard, 1983, 1985, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - "The Last Tycoon" - CBS Radio Broadcast Script, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Last Will and Testament to Yoshio Kishi, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Letter and Receipt, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Lincoln Terrace Maps, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - List of Medical Expenses, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Livre de France, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Medical Letter from Mitsugu Shimmyo, MD, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clipping -- "Best Cameras for $300 or Less", 2010 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - New York Nichibei Newspaper Photocopies, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - New York Travel Service Receipts, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Personal Correspondence and Journal Entries, 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 17-20)
  - Personal Notebook, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 21-22)
  - Personal Reflection - Yoshio Kishi, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Photograph, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Photographs -- Daily Life, undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Photographs -- Family (originals), 1910-1980 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Photographs -- Kishi's Apartment, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Photographs -- Personal, 1986, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Photo Negatives -- Ma + Iyls, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Photo Negatives of Everyday Life, undated (Box 12, Folder 6, Box 13, Folder 1-4)
  - Receipts, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Rita Takahashi, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Sumi-e Painting Exhibit, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - VHS Tape -- Yoshio Kishi Interview, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Villiers De L'Isle, 1919, 2000, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Wilson, Colin, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Yoshio Kishi - Personal and Family Information, 1991-1994 (Box 12, Folder 16)